Aurel Jared C. Dantis

Quezon City, Philippines

台 October 4, 2000

% +63 (949) 416 6041

□ acdantis@up.edu.ph

in jareddantis



Profile

Computer science undergraduate with a passion for the visual arts and a desire to unite timely information with good design. Has experience creating websites, promotional materials, and other media for various purposes, ranging from personal projects to academic requirements and events.

Education

University of the Philippines Diliman

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science · 2019 – present

Philippine Science High School Main Campus

Secondary · 2013 – 2019

University of the Philippines Integrated School

Primary · 2006 – 2013

Skills

Frontend Web Development

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

jQuery

CSS preprocessors (SCSS, Less, Stylus)

Vue.js 2 + Vuetify

Backend Web Development

PHP

MySQL

Adobe Creative Cloud

Photoshop

Illustrator

InDesign

Lightroom

Premiere Pro

Other

Sketch

Experience

Info & PR Head, UP CURSOR 1920A Talents Night

Oct 2019

Led the information and public relations committee for the UP CURSOR Talents Night of Batch 1920A, in the creation of the batch branding, profile pictures, and event publicity materials.

Publicity Committee Member, BRAIN BLAST!

Dec 2018 - Jan 2019

Designed branding, print, and digital media for the annual PSHS-MC research fair, featuring research projects in different fields by select Grade 12 students.

Lead Graphic Designer, IMPETU Benefit Concert

Apr 2018

Designed branding, print, and digital media for the PSHS-MC EPTC's benefit concert.

Layout Artist, Ang Lagablab

Aug 2016 - May 2017

Redesigned visual identity and typeset issues for the official PSHS-MC student publication in the Filipino language.

Event Co-organizer, PSHS-MC Interschool IT Challenge

Mar 2017

Facilitated program and designed identity & digital media for the PSHS-MC annual computer science quiz bee.

Media Associate, Hijinks Fair

Feb 2017

Designed website and print media for the annual PSHS-MC school fair.

Workshops & conferences attended

Iskolart

Nov 2018

Conference on the application of design in an educational context, and the state of art in current Philippine society.

PSHSS 2018 Science Research Summit

Sep - Oct 2018

Convention of PSHS scholars from all over the Philippines that aims to increase the community's knowledge and appreciation of Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics (STEM).

Annual conference on the current state of and trends in design, with talks from veterans of various fields in the industry.

TEDxYouth@PSHSMain

May 2017

Conference that aims to spark discussion and connection through talks given by experts from various fields, from mathematics to the arts.

Awards & citations

Oblation Scholarship Awardee

University of the Philippines Diliman

Undergraduate Merit Scholarship Awardee

Science Education Institute, Department of Science and Technology

Consistent Director's Lister

Philippine Science High School Main Campus

Champion, 9th Grace Information Technology Inter-school Quiz Bee

Grace Christian College, Quezon City

6th Place, Pagsulat ng Balita

Division of Secondary Schools Press Conference (DSSPC) 2016

Hobbies &

Playman

https://playman.jared.gg/

projects

A web app for quickly managing your Spotify playlists, even while on the go. Supports shuffling, merging, backups and more.

General Weighted Average (GWA) Calculator

https://calc.jared.gg/

A web app for students that lets them quickly estimate their current class standing.